<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Drambo Docs]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Drambo Docs</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:24:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:24:19 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Drambo Notes]]></title><description><![CDATA[Drambo is an innovative modular groovebox and audio processing environment. Modular components are used to build synthesized and sample based instruments and audio effects using high-quality DSP and audio-rate modulation. Tied to a powerful sequencer, it’s an optimal music creation tool for sound design, composition, performance, and experimentationAt the heart of Drambo lies an entirely new concept that makes modularity easy, fun and affordable. Modules are connected automatically, with no cables as you add or rearrange them. A dynamic interface creates modulation knobs when you need them. Modules may house other modules, so you can keep your patch well organized. Of course, automatic connections can be overridden. In Drambo you can focus on playing with sound and signal structure without getting lost in wires.Use a deep and innovative sequencer to compose patterns and whole tracks, for production or live performance. Go beyond simple looping sequences with parameter locking, conditional step components, and powerful scene morphing. Drambo works equally well as a self-contained standalone app or audio unit plugin with audio and MIDI connectivity as an AUV3 instrument, audio effect, and midi effect. No modular experience necessary to get started playing with preset sounds and effects.Unique modular concept: cable-less, drag'n'drop, color coding dynamic interface, automatic connections, and customizable compact, rack views.Directional flow (helps in better overview). There are no instant feedback routings in Drambo. Delayed feedback is possible using certain modules.Simple and clean interface, that scales to every size and device orientationCustom modular racks, presets on different levels.Polyphonic, stereo processing. Audio-rate modulation. All signals are equal.Multiple modulators per parameter without additional mixer modules.Polyphonic step sequencer&nbsp;with parameter locks and step components. Up to 64 beats and 256 steps per pattern.Over 120 modules available, such as: oscillators, samplers, physical modelling modules, LFOs, envelope generators, filters, audio effects mixers, MIDI processors, sequencers and math functions.Morph groups: you can morph many parameters using a single slider.Audio Units hosting. Instrument, effect and MIDI effect AUv3s are visible as Drambo modules.Available as a standalone app, AUv3 instrument, effect and midi effect.MIDI support A complete music production and performance environment. Endless modular playground, that allows you to build, modify and store custom instruments and effects. For instance:build a custom synth, sample and resample, build a Theremin using a gyroscope module, or turn your table into a playable surface, by processing microphone input with physical modelling modules. Get weird or make functional instruments and tools. MIDI sequencer, that works with hardware and AUv3 instruments (e.g. Drambo sequences other instruments in an AU host app). Moreover Drambo can generate custom MIDI CC messages or modulation signals to control modular synths via DC coupled interfaces. AUv3 synthesizer, effect or sequencer in other DAWs. Concept, development, UI design: Jaroslaw Jacek (BeepStreet 2020)
<a data-href="Modules" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/modules.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Modules</a> <br><a data-href="AMP" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/amp.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AMP</a>
<br><a data-href="AU" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/au.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AU</a>
<br><a data-href="CONVERT" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/convert.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CONVERT</a>
<br><a data-href="CV" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/cv.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CV</a>
<br><a data-href="ENV" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/env.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">ENV</a>
<br><a data-href="FILTER" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/filter.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">FILTER</a>
<br><a data-href="FX" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/fx.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">FX</a>
<br><a data-href="LFO" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/lfo.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">LFO</a>
<br><a data-href="MATH" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/math.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">MATH</a>
<br><a data-href="MIDI" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/midi.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">MIDI</a>
<br><a data-href="MIXER" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/mixer.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">MIXER</a>
<br><a data-href="OSC" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/osc.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">OSC</a>
<br><a data-href="RACK" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/rack.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">RACK</a>
<br><a data-href="SAMPLER" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/sampler.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">SAMPLER</a>
<br><a data-href="SEQ" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/seq.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">SEQ</a>
<br><a data-href="SHAPER" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/shaper.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">SHAPER</a>
<br><a data-href="UI" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/ui.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">UI</a>
<br><a data-href="UTILS" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/utils.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">UTILS</a> <br><a data-href="Songs" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/songs/songs.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Songs</a>
<br><a data-href="Tags" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/tags/tags.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Tags</a>
<br><a data-href="Templates" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/templates/templates.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Templates</a>
<br><a data-href="Patches" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/patches/patches.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Patches</a>
A container module for custom instruments. All signal inputs are passed to the internal rack which outputs an audio signal. Instrument rack works in two modes, that you can set in module's menu: CV - Instrument is controlled by CV signals: Pitch, Gate and Velocity.
MIDI - Instrument is controlled by MIDI signal, that is converted into CV signals.
A container module for custom sound processor. All signal inputs are passed to internal rack which outputs an audio signal.A container module for your custom MIDI/Generator A flexible rack container with a configurable number of inputs and outputs. Hit + to add socket. Double tap on socket to edit its type.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/drambo-notes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Drambo Notes.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[00-Drambo Cookbook]]></title><description><![CDATA[
Possibly an HTML site? Rip Text from initial start by JJ if not - Doc site from Pikapods GIFS of all Modules? Tutorial Explanations Check Drambo Docs WIKI started on Forum
EXPORT HTML WEBPAGE OBSIDIAN PLUGIN ① = 1 Voice, Monophonic Module. symbols xtal symbols 1
icomoonPubbii - 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<a rel="noopener nofollow" class="external-link is-unresolved" href="https://offbrands-studio.github.io/drambo/" target="_self">https://offbrands-studio.github.io/drambo/</a>Start with LIBRARY GENERATOR
PROCESSOR
MODULATOR
MIXER
MIDI
MISC / UTILITY MATH
VISUAL TAGS AMP
AU
CONVERT CV
ENV
FILTER
FX
LFO
MATH
MIDI
MIXER
OSC
RACK
SAMPLER SEQ
SHAPER
UI
UTILS 14h 40m 56s14.68hTotalBlock Name:Copy MarkdownCopy CSVCopy JSONSave PDF
<br><a data-href="Drambo Notes" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/drambo-notes.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Drambo Notes</a>
]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/00-drambo-cookbook.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/00-Drambo Cookbook.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UI]]></title><description><![CDATA[Generate CV signals by rotating your iDevice around its X, Y, Z axis.A constant value signal generator. Useful for user-adjustable math operations and direct control of modulation values. Can output signal values between -1.0 and 1.0Adjust multiple values. Add more knobs with "+". Useful for user-adjustable math operations and direct control of modulation values. Can output signal values between -1.0 and 1.0 and be modulated if desired. Double-tap on a knob to configure it. Move up/down for quick adjustment of left/right for fine adjustment. A grid of buttons. Slide up to configure each button.A very handy monitoring and debugging utility. If something in your magic cration doesn't work as expected, make sure you look at different signals using the Oscilloscope. Set the Threshold value to minimum and play with X and Y scale knobs to make sure you don't miss the shown waveform. The oscilloscope screen also shows maximum and minimum numbers with some averaging applied to make them more readable. No module help yet. Come back later please :)A constant value signal generator. Sends a value between 0..1 depending on fader position.A single universal button that can work in either momentary or switch mode. Touch and drag upwards on the button to configure it. Document your project directly on the Ul! If the Text Box is too big, try the "Section" module.Provides a button which generates a short Gate signal by tapping on it. A touchable X/Y pad that translates the crosshair position to 2 bipolar CV signals (from -1 to 1). Upon touch, a gate signal is generated.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/ui.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/UI.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UTILS]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Morph module can be used to modulate any parameter. It lets you modulate parameters without a modulation input (small triangle left to the knob). Tap on ASSIGN and turn the destination knob by the amount that you want Morph to be effective. Multiple parameters can be mapped on the track that holds a Morph module, while morph amount can be modulated by external modulation sources, such as env, LFO etc.This module sends a delayed signal to a corresponding Feedback receive module. Connect the Fdb receive port to the Feedback Receive module that is placed before the Feedback send module. A delayed signal will be transmitted to the Feedback Receive module in the opposite direction! (from right to left). This module is a great tool for advanced self modulations or feedback if a short delay doesn't matter. Tip: Check the Tutorials/Feedback modules project.Receives signal from Feedback send module. Must be placed left from the related Feedback Send module. Tip: Check the Tutorials/Feedback modules project. Detects transients and isolates them in the outuput signal. Additional gate and velocity signals are generated. Each voice is converted to many voices with pitch spread to achieve a unisono effect. If the number of output voices is greater than all available track voices (16), input voices are ignored. Example: If voices param is set to 4, only 2 input voices will be active (4*2=8). Set MIDI to CV number of voices to 2. Generates a polyphonic signal in which each voice carries its own voice number. Select one voice from a polyphonic signal and output it as a single-voice signal.Utility to create stepped ramp up modulation, based on incoming TRIG/GATE signals. You can define how many steps it takes to reach the peak (and then repeat), and apply smoothing to steps. Tip: Use it to create a custom time signal.Pulse Divider module divides the frequency of the incoming pulses by integer ratios. Utility to create continuous, tempo based modulation/transition. Define duration for transition and p-lock its direction. Generates a random number upon each received Gate impulse. Enter the highest number to generate in the number field.• bipolar=off: Generate a number between 0 and the pre-set value. • bipolar=on: Generate a number between the negative and the positive pre-set value.Generate CV signals by rotating your iDevice around its X, Y, Z axis.For use in Wavetable oscillator rack.
==15 modulatable wavetable effects: ==
Saturate Expand
Clip Fold Bit redux Warp 1 Warp 2 Warp 3 PWM Hard sync Flip Wrap Ring mod Normalize Phase Multiply Dbl wrap Resample Fractal Unipolar Chop Bitmask phase For use in Wavetable oscillator rack. Advanced spectral filter with 3 filter types, modulatable cutoff frequency and filter tilt (up to -infinite db/ oct which allows e.g. for hard cutting overtones). A wave effect adding slight variations to an otherwise static sounding wavetable. Can help to make a waveform sound more alive, especially if the wavetable index is used for other purposes. Use with spectral signals like in Wavetable oscillator. A wave effect applying the spectrum of an input signal to the current signal. Use with spectral signals like in Wavetable oscillator. No module help yet. Come back later please :)External audio input. Converts incoming CV signals (gate, pitch and time) into Eurorack modular format. Use this module to control external analog gears using a DC coupled audio interface.Generates a polyphonic value, where each knob sets signal level for corresponding voice. Tip: use to provide mismatch between voices, like in vintage analog synths. e.g. Set knobs to random values and modulate Oscillator Tune param.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/utils.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/UTILS.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SEQ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Generates modulation values set in a simple CV style sequencer. It's driven by a Time signal by default. When a gate signal is connected, the sequencer advances only on a rising gate signal. Reset input sets playback position to zero (works only in gate mode).May be used as a table lookup module.Generate clock (gate) pulses from the received time signal. You can choose how many pulses per beat are generated. You could use multiple modules to derive different rhythmic meters to generate polyrhythms, for example.Generates gate and velocity values set in a simple CV style sequencer. It's driven by a Time signal by default. When a gate signal is connected, the sequencer advances only on a rising gate signal. Reset input sets playback position to zero (works only in gate mode). May be used as a table lookup module.Generates multiple triggers (a pulse train) out of one Gate trigger signal. "Duration" and "Density" set the number of beats in the pulse train, "Steps/beat" adjusts the length of one pulse, "Bend duration" and "Bend amount" optionally control and increase or decrease in pulse frequency, and "Bend velo" acts like an Attack control (to the left) or Decay control (to the right) on the velocity signal.Creates Gate impulses stochastically distributed over time, much like a Geiger counter or dust on a vinyl record. Some people would call this a random impulse generator.Euclidean sequencer: Divide a number of beat subdivisions over a time interval and place MIDI notes as evenly as possible into the sequence. Generated events are mixed into an incoming MIDI stream, so this module may be chained to generate different notes on the same track. Use the Time swing module before for beat shuffling.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/seq.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/SEQ.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SHAPER]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bit depth reduction of the input signal. The signal is quantized to the adjusted bit depth, and the number of quantization steps is equivalent to 2 (# of Bits).Generates pulse wave that fits zero crossings or peaks of incoming signal.Resample the input signal with an adjustable sample rate. (aliasing-supressed version)A Waveshaper that lets you draw any shaping curve. Can shape any kind of CV signal. Tip: Use it after a SAW wave oscillator with "Anti-aliasing"=Off to draw your own phantasy waveform.A multimode waveshaper with different shaping presets. 3 saturation modes and 2 folding modes are available. Bias greater than zero turns on DC offset blocker.Pulse Divider module divides the frequency of the incoming pulses by integer ratios.Sample and Hold: With every gate impulse, store the current value of the input signal and send it to the module output. The output remains constant until the next gate signal triggers sampling of the input value again.Delays the rising or falling of a signal by sweeping from one value to the other.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/shaper.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/SHAPER.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SAMPLER]]></title><description><![CDATA[A sophisticated sampler with a multitude of operating modes.• 1-Shot - play the sample once. • 1-Slice - play current slice once. Which slice to play depends on the setting in "Start slice".• Loop - play sample in loop mode from Offset to Loop end, then again from Loop start.• Loop p-pong - the same as above, but loop is playing bidirectionally• Scratch - playhead is stopped and controlled by Offset parameter. Modulate offset e.g. with oscillators or Ifo to scrub through the sample.• Pitch - the sample pitch in semitones• Speed - bidirectional playback speed.
• Positive value: play forward from Offset position.
• Negative value: play backwards from Loop end position. Time stretching is active if "Stretching" is enabled in the module header menu and if you have set the number of beats in the loop in the "Sync" field.A simple one shot sampler. Samples containing markers are chopped and slices are played randomly (round-robin).A multi zone sampler. Select "Load folder" from module menu to automatically load samples folder.Samples can be auto-mapped if the imported file names match this pattern: • Filename_Notenumber_Velocity.wav • Filename: Any name that does not contain numbers or special characters • Notenumber: A number between 0 and 127 that will be mapped to the corresponding key in Sampler. The root key will default to that key as • Velocity: A number between 1 and 127&nbsp;Imported samples will be sorted to the velocity ranges 1...31, 32...63, 64...95 and 96...127. There is no 1-to-1 mapping so that if you import 4 samples with velocity 1, 2, 3 and 4 to the same note, they will be distributed over the whole velocity range.Wave scanner freezes the sound at the current playhead position. The module uses an advanced spectral resynthesis technique. Sounds cleaner than granular synthesis in most cases. It's a great companion to Radio Unit AUv3 by BeepStreet :).]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/sampler.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/SAMPLER.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RACK]]></title><description><![CDATA[A container module for custom instruments. All signal inputs are passed to the internal rack which outputs an audio signal. Instrument rack works in two modes, that you can set in module's menu: CV - Instrument is controlled by CV signals: Pitch, Gate and Velocity.
MIDI - Instrument is controlled by MIDI signal, that is converted into CV signals.
A container module for custom sound processor. All signal inputs are passed to internal rack which outputs an audio signal.A container module for your custom MIDI/Generator A flexible rack container with a configurable number of inputs and outputs. Hit + to add socket. Double tap on socket to edit its type.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/rack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/RACK.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OSC]]></title><description><![CDATA[Similar to main Oscillator. Has additional Sine Nine and Sine PD shapes. Pulse Width knob also controls phase distortion amount in Sine PD shape. Ideal FM modulator.A standard subtractive-style oscillator with a variety of waveforms and modulation inputs for pitch and pulse width. Pulse width adjustment is only available when the Pulse waveform is selected. Tip: Add one of the pitch modules before for more precise pitch adjustment.an ultra-clean wavetable oscillator. Support for Serum wavetable format (WT frames each with 2048 samples length), up to 256 waves in a single oscillator, morphing, 7 voices stereo unison, modulatable Position, audio-rate modulatable Phase and Tune, modular wavetable manipulation. The Wavetable oscillator contains an internal rack for advanced wavetable effects, using additional modules like Wave effect and Wave filter. Tap on the rack icon in the bottom-right corner to open the internal rack that is used for additional wavetable processing.Use the Wave effect and Wave filter modules from PROCESSOR / Spectral section.41 great wavetables created by Echo Sound Works included. You can also import standard wave files that are not dedicated wavetables (and therefore won't scan as smoothlv).A perfect emulation of the famous JP8K supersaw oscillator. (7 detuned saw waves)The basic element (operator) of FM synthesis.
An internal oscillator's frequency or phase is linearly modulated by FM input (autoconnected). Internal feedback changes oscillator waveshape from square wave through sine to saw. Frequency ratio may be set to zero. In this case the FM Operator "is stopped" and acts like a sophisticated waveshaper / through-zero oscillator.
FM Amount - controls how much modulator (connected to FM input) affects FM modulation.
Ratio - base frequency ratio
Detune - base frequency detune
Mod - Phase / Freq - switch between phase or linear frequency modulation
Feedback - amount of output signal that is internally fed back to FM input. Changes waveshape: square-sine-saw
Attack, Decay - set attack and decay length of internal amp envelope
Retrig - Determines if oscillator should restart phase on each trigger
Velocity - amount of velocity influence on amp envelope level
End level - bottom level of amplitude envelope generator
Combine several FM Operators in serries or using mixer to achieve different FM structures.
Noise generator. Allows for choosing between "White" and "Pink" noise which has less high frequency content. Switch to stereo for uncorrelated stereo noise. Polyphony: If you want to have separate noise source per voice, connect gate input to polyphonic gate output.Create a short impulse from Gate and Velocity inputs. Impulse shape depends on the Shape setting and the impulse length can be adjusted between super-narrow and up to 50ms. Noise allows you to add noise with the same envelope as the impulse and Tone is a simple 6dB low pass filter to further shape the signal. Useful but not limited to creating excitation impulses for the Modal Resonator, Comb Filter and others. A physically-informed digital model of famous TR808 kick generator cirucit.Sunthesizes and approximates the human voice by generating vowel sounds (and more).These can be manipulated to provide deep low baritones or high pitched squeaks.Use Formant parameter to morph between 5 vowels, that you set use a row of select controls on the right side.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/osc.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/OSC.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MIXER]]></title><description><![CDATA[A flexible mixer. You can add multiple channels for mixing by tapping the "+" sign and choosing the signal output icon of the module you want to add to the mix. Make sure you add knobs in the correct order, they cannot be moved afterwards. Each knob will be given the name of the module so if you want to change it, change the module name.Layers switch holds a number of parallel racks with only one of them being connected to the output. Choose which layer is connected by either hitting one of the track buttons or applying a signal between 0.0 and 1.0 on the index input, which will be mapped to the whole range of buttons you have (0.0=first, 1.0=last layer)
"CPU save" tells Drambo what to do with layers other than the chosen &amp; connected layer. CPU save = on: Disable processing in all layers but the currently selected one CPU save = off: Keep processing all layers, no matter if selected or not. You may need this in delay or reverb effects for example, when audio needs to be processed in advance to get the desired effect when switching to the respective layer. Crossfade between inputs. The A/B knob middle position is a 50/50 mix of both signals. A super-simple signal mixer that adds all connected signals to one output signal. No adjustments except choosing the signals from modules you want to include. Double-tap on a signal icon to disconnect and remove it.Layers module. Holds a number of parallel racks. You may add, remove or rename them. Only one rack is visible at a time, so it's a great tool for simplifying the visual structure. Outputs of all racks are summed at the main module output. Layers mixer module holds a number of parallel racks. You may add, remove or rename them. Only one rack is visible at a time, so it's a great tool for simplifying the visual structure.Layers mixer module. Holds a number of parallel racks. You may add, remove or rename them. Only one rack is visible at a time, so its a great tool for making visual structure simpler. Each layer has corresponding volume knob. Outputs of all racks are summed at the main module output. Input signal is divided into 3 frequency bands (configurable via 2 Freq knobs). Each band is processed by a separate layer and mixed down at the end. 2 band split filter slopes are available: 12dB/oct and 24dB/oct. By default, the module mixes down a polyphonic signal to a mono voice (to save CPU). Use the poly option for polyphonic processing. Provides stereo panning. Routes the input signal to the selected output. Use the Index input to select input index via external signal (normalized value 0-1). 3 switch modes are available:
• Instant.
• X-Fade - when Index input value is fractional, outputs are cross faded.
• Smooth - transitions are smoothed out.Routes one of the input signals to the module's output. Use Index input to select output index via external signal (normalized value 0-1).3 switch modes are available:
• Instant
• X-Fade - when Index input value is fractional, inputs are cross faded.
• Smooth - transitions are smoothed out. ]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/mixer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/MIXER.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MATH]]></title><description><![CDATA[Add two input signals.Divide the signal value of Input 1 by the signal value of Input 2. Negative numbers are supported. Divide by zero is eliminated and will return a very high result instead.Offers a choice of preset operations on the two input channels.• A+B: Add the values of A and B
• A-B: Subtract B from A.
• A*B: Multiply A by B.
• Maximum: Always output the higher one of the two input values.
• Minimum: Always output the lower one of the two input values.
• A&gt;B: Outputs 1 if A is higher than B, otherwise O • B&gt;A: Outputs 1 if B is higher than A, otherwise 0Find and forward the higher value of two input signals.Find and forward the lower value of two input signals.Multiplies input values.Calculate the difference between the two input signals.Calculates the reciprocal (multiplicative inverse) of the input value. Clips the input signal to Low and High range.Calculates exponential function of the input signal.Mirrors the lower half of the input signal (below the waveform zero line) to the upper half.
Derived from an electronic bridge rectifier with four diodes. Creates even more overtones than the Half Rectifier.Cuts away the lower half of the input signal (below the waveform zero line). Derived from a simple electronic rectifier with one diode only. Adds overtones to the signal.Cuts away the lower half of the input signal (below the waveform zero line). Derived from a simple electronic rectifier with one diode only. Adds overtones to the signal. Calculates continous integral of incoming signal.Sends a difference between current and previous signal value.Calculate the logarithmic of the input signal. Useful for compressing the lower range and expanding the upper range of values.
Expects a positive signal at the input. Input values at or below zero will result in Output=zero.
If you want to make use of the full scale of a bipolar input signal, make sure you add an appropriate offset to it before feeding it this module.A signal generator that provides a pre-set DC signal. The entered value can be positive or negative. Adds a constant value to the input signal.Round incoming signal to the nearest integer value. (e.g. 1,2 -&gt; 1). Use the Scale or Scale&amp;Offset modules to adapt it to the signal level.A signal scaler that can boost or attenuate a signal. Range is the preamp gain, it can also be a negative number like -0.34.Calculate the sine function of the input signal.Calculates the square root of the input signal. Input values at or below zero always result in zero. If you want to make use of the full scale of a bipolar input signal, make sure you add a positive offset to the input signal before connecting it to this module.Logical AND gate. Output is 1 only when both inputs are greater than zero.Logical OR gate. Output is 1 only when one of inputs is greater than zero.Logical eXclusive-OR gate. Output is 1 if only one of the inputs is 1. If both inputs have the same logical level then the output is zero.Logical negation. All values equal or below 0 turn into 1. Greater than 0 turn into 1.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/math.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/MATH.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[MIDI]]></title><description><![CDATA[Convert incoming MIDI CC events into a modulation CV signal. Press the Learn button and move a MIDI controller to assign a CC number automatically.A MIDI message monitor. Can read and display incoming messages as well as messages from internal MIDI modules.Note: Not all messages are shown in order to keep the display readable.Provides a dedicated MIDI input from the selected MIDI port. "Channel" lets you choose which MIDI channel to receive from. "Omni" means: Receive MIDI from all channels 1 to 16. Send incoming MIDI to an external MIDI output.Turn incoming MIDI data into corresponding CV signals: Gate, pitch and velocity.Turns internal CV signal into midi CC message to be used to control or modulate external AUv3, IAA or hardware.Select the CC number from the drop down menu and route its output to a Midi Output module.Use knobs to generate many MIDI CC messages and mix them into incoming MIDI stream. Knobs are modulatable. Double tap on a knob to set CC number.Turns internal Note - gate, velocity, pitchsignals into midi Note message, so various CV generator and sequencer modules can be used to drive external AUv3, IAA or hardware. Route its output to Midi Output module.No module help yet. Come back later please :)Arp allows the player to automatically step through a sequence of notes based on the player's input, thus creating an arpeggio. Its a MIDI effect plugin, so use it with MIDI signals (put the module before MIDI 2 CV or Instrument rack in MIDI mode).• Rate, Sync - set playback frequency, tempo synchronization mode (modulatable).
• Gate - Set gate length (modulatable).
• Host sync - When active, generated MIDI events are synchronized with host tempo, in other case sequence starts as soon as you press the first key.• Range - Number of octaves, the sequence goes through.
• Mode - up, up and down, down, random, as play. Defines the direction of the sequence.Optional gate input: When connected, the internal ARP sequencer is triggered only on gate signal. Euclidean sequencer: Divide a number of beat subdivisions over a time interval and place MIDI notes as evenly as possible into the sequence. Generated events are mixed into an incoming MIDI stream, so this module may be chained to generate different notes on the same track. Use the Time swing module before for beat shuffling.Depending on type setting, it passes only MIDI note/cc messages on specific channel (Filter) or sets a fixed channel to all incoming MIDI messages (Set). Tip: Use two of these modules to build MIDI channel based routings.Create a chord by adding additional voices to incoming midi Note(s). Use knobs to define how each additional voice should be shifted in semitones) from incoming midi Note(s).Chords with up to 6 voices can be created.
Keeping a knob at its default position "0" will not add another voice to the chord.Latches incoming MIDI notes when Latch button is active. Works in 2 modes: replace - replaces all latched notes each time a new note is coming toggle - incoming notes are added to existing latched notes pool.
Add probability to an incoming midi Note. Enable Chord mode to add probability to each note of an incoming chord.Signal delay, modulatable and adjustable between 0.0ms and 1.0s delay time. Varies note values like velocity and note length (gate) and can push notes back with random offset.Merges MIDI signals from different MIDI sources.Combines multiple MIDI inputs into a single output. Each input may be muted.A MIDI-aware switch to route one input to one of multiple outputs. Will take care of correctly handling MIDI Note messages (i.e. sending Note Off messages when a MIDI port with sustained notes is switched away from).Use drop down menus to define a range of notes, where From will become the lowest and To will become the highest note of the range.
All notes outside of the range will be filtered out.A polyphonic MIDI voice distributor. The incoming MIDI signal is divided into voices and sent to 4 MIDI outputs, each representing a separate voice.Generates MIDI pitch bend message.Retriggers incoming MIDI Note messages. You can set rate, beat division and velocity.Play a chord split into its individual notes. Requires that all chord notes start (and optionally end) at the same time.Transpose incoming midi Note(s) by Amount * Interval (in semitones).
A quick and effortless way to transpose musical phrases up and down when turning patterns into songs. A midi 'guide track' of sorts...]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/midi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/MIDI.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[LFO]]></title><description><![CDATA[A classic Low Frequency Oscillator with different waveforms. LFO frequency can either be adjusted and modulated freely or be synced to beat fractions. The waveform can be forced to start at a certain phase using the Gate input and Phase knob. • Freq - frequency • Sync - time base, other options than Freq keeps LFO synchronized with current tempo • Amount - modulation amount • Bipolar - output signal range: -1 to 1 for bipolar and 0 to 1 for non bipolar; • Phase - Modulatable LFO phase (continuous modulation). Use 2nd LFO for interesting phase modulated curves. If you want to set start phase use a signal latched on gate, e.g. Random module or SH with gate and another LFO. • Waveform - Sine, Triangle, Saw up, Saw down, Square, Sample'n'Hold, Random sine, Random triangle, and SH rampA simplified Low Frequency Oscillator with different waveforms. Can be synced to bpm using the Time signal input which will let the Freq knob adjust its speed related to beats. • Freq - frequency • Amount - modulation amount • Bipolar - output signal range: -1 to 1 for bipolar and 0 to 1 for non bipolar. • Waveform - Sine, Triangle, Saw up, Saw down, Square.If you connect the Time input, this LFO runs in synchronized mode.A simplified stereo Low Frequency Oscillator with different waveforms. Can be synced to bpm using the Time signal input which will let the Freq knob adjust its speed related to beats. • Freq - frequency. • Phase - phase difference between left and right signal. • Amount - modulation amount. • Bipolar - output signal range: -1 to 1 for bipolar and 0 to 1 for non bipolar. • Waveform - Sine, Triangle, Saw up, Saw down, Square, Sample'n'Hold and SH ramp. • Sym - if active, the phase between L and R channels is shifted symmetrically. If you connect the Time input, this LFO works in synchronized mode.Customize shapes and use them as LFO modulation sources. From super-slow up to audio rate. Connect GATE input to launch it at any time and use a polyphonic GATE signal to control polyphony.A powerful LFO that can use the same wavetables as in the WT oscillator but at low speeds and in sync with pattern time. ]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/lfo.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/LFO.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FILTER]]></title><description><![CDATA[A classic linear multimode filter. 9 modes available, from 6 to 24 poles.Advanced audio filter based on analog models.• TR6 TR - transistor ladder 6db/oct low pass filter
• LP12 SK1 - 12db/oct low pass filter.
• LP24 TR - transistor ladder 24db/oct low pass filter
• LP24 OTA - op amp ladder 24db/oct low pass filter
• MM12 OB - multimode filter, Tone knob morphs between LP throught Notch to HP
• LP12 FDB - a funky 12db/oct low pass filter with additional feedback loop. Filter output modulates cutoff frequency (Tone knob)A comb filter is a filter implemented by adding a delayed version of a signal to itself, causing constructive and destructive interference.Waveguide is like a comb filter with 2 additional filters inside LPF or BPF and nonlinear APF. It's a nice tool for simulating physical objects like tubes. Tips: Audiorate modulate APF or LPF filter. In BPF mode, keep BP filter frequency close to the main frequency.A parametric peaking equalizer filter that provides a boost or cut in the vicinity of the adjusted center frequency.Modal Resonator emulates the resonance properties of membranes, strings and tubes.Adds characteristics of the human voice to a sound. Use Formant parameter to morph between 5 vowels, that you set use a row of select controls on the right side.A creative resonator/distortion effect, that incorporates variable sample rate processing and feedback modulation.An IFFT filter that uses curve to shape spectral content of incoming signal.Window parameter affects frequency resolution. Larger window sizes provide better frequency resolution but also introduce latency.Due to delay this filter is not suitable for processing sources that depend on realtime events (e.g. MIDI), but it's a great tool for filtering noise or other constant sources.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/filter.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/FILTER.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[FX]]></title><description><![CDATA[On each incoming trigger, a portion of the input signal is sampled to a buffer and played in a loop.
Loop length is determined by the Pitch parameter.On each synchronized cycle (defined by Size param), the incoming signal is recorded and replayed with defined Speed (bidirectional) Buffers are crossfaded to prevent clicks.Loop and repeat incoming signal. Buffer size is tempo synchronized.Simulates tape start / stop effect. note: tape start is crossfaded with original signal. It's not possible to make tape start for realtime signal without lookahead or latencyDJ style EQ with fixed curves and frequencies. • Low - low shelf @100Hz
• Mid - peak @ 1.5kHz
• High - high shelf @10kHzA Classic Chorus effect that can be run in either mono or stereo configuration. The effect signal is always mixed with the input signal, an effect-only signal is not available.A classic dynamics compressor with lookahead and RMS mode.Signal delay, modulatable and adjustable between 0.0ms and 1.0s delay time.An audio delay that can either be freely adjusted between 20ms and 2.5s or synchronized to adjustable beat divisions (based on 3/4 and 4/4 beats). Dry/Wet adjusts the original vs effect levels. The rightmost setting will emit the delayed effect signal only. A Delay with an internal rack that is used to process the signal in the feedback loop.Shifts all the frequencies in the input signal up or down by a certain amount. This kind of shifting will ruin the harmonic footprint of the input signal, making it sound dissonant. • Amount - linear amount of frequency shift from (-Range to Range), zero = no shift • Range - exponential range in Hz in which Amount param works. The output shift is: Amount * exponential (Range). Tips: If you want to modulate shift exponentially then modulate the Range knob. If you want to modulate shift in a linear manner then modulate the Amount knob. If you want shift by tracking the current keyboard frequency then modulate the Range param with keyboard frequency (= Pitch signal) Noise gate is a specific case of the dynamics processor. It removes parts of the signal with levels below the selected threshold. Signal is smoothed by attack, hold, release envelope.
Envelope detector signal is available at additional output: SG env. You may use it for further processing, e.g. control filter cutoff. Use sidechain input to use other signal for envelope detection.A classic 6 stages phaser with feedback. (zerodelay technique) A flanger works by mixing two identical audio signals together, with one of the signals playing at a slightly slower speed. This creates the effect of two tape recordings playing simultaneously, but with one tape player going slightly slower than the other.The pitch shifter changes the pitch of an incoming audio signal. It adds some latency. A simple but very useful convolution (IR) processor. Multiplies the spectrum of the input signal with the spectrum of the loaded impulse response. Can be used for EQ, delays, reverbs etc. but cannot replicate amplitude dependent characteristics (to add these, use the Graphic shaper). An algorithmic reverb audio effect based on a delay feedback network. Lush and precise. An algorithmic reverb audio effect based on a plate model.Reduces the stereo signal width (i.e. L/R channel differences) by an adjustable amount. If one channel is the perfectly phase-reversed (inverted, negated) version of the other channel, setting Width to zero will result in no sound output.This module loops incoming audio signal according to incoming MIDI notes, that represent step position in a bar. Use it on a send track, e.g. Master.Punch-in FX module is a set of effect layers, each activated by incoming MIDI note (piano key). Use it on a send track, e.g. Master.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/fx.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/FX.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[ENV]]></title><description><![CDATA[Attack/Decay envelope generator with Sustain mode and Velocity control. Attack/Decay envelope modulator with modulatable parameters.Attack/Decay/Sustain/Release envelope generator with Velocity support. A Gate signal triggers the adjusted envelope shape which is then scaled by the received velocity and sent to the output.Variable shape envelope generator. Shape parameter morphs curve from pulse like, through classical exponential decay (zero) to vactrol like curve. Turn on Cumulate parameter if you want envelope value to be accumulated on each trigger.An envelope generator with freely definable shape, built from polylines. Hit the graph window to open the full-size editor. Tap anywhere on the line to add a point and tap on an existing point to remove it. • Length is the total length of the envelope shape from left to right.
• Don't forget to add an Amplifier if you want to use the shape as a volume envelope and use this module's output as a modulator for the Amp gain, for example.Detects the volume of a signal over time. Attack and Decay controls adjust the volume detection speed. If you want to detect short transients, keep the Attack control low enough.
If you want to avoid too quick jumps in the detected signal at the same time, you can increase the Decay value for example. Amount controls the output gain and can have positive or negative polarity. The center value of the Amount knob is zero.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/env.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/ENV.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CV]]></title><description><![CDATA[Adds pitch glide for notes played or sequenced in legato (new note on received before old note off).Important: Disable MIDI &gt; Retrigger in the track header menu for this to work. Quantizes incoming pitch CV signal into the nearest selected note.Detunes incoming pitch CV signal by overtone or undertone. (Frequency is multiplied by integer values) Converts pitch CV signal to linear frequency.Converts linear frequency to pitch CV signal.Turn incoming MIDI data into corresponding CV signals: Gate, pitch and velocity. ]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/cv.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/CV.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CONVERT]]></title><description><![CDATA[Merge 2 separate left and right signals to one stereo signal.Duplicates a mono-voiced input to a polyphonic signal. Tips: This module may be used to launch a bunch of sounds on a single trigger.
Pass gate through Mono to Poly, then to a Delay module modulated by e.g. Random modulator.
Converts a mono signal to stereo. Mix down a polyphonic signal to 1 voice. This module is crucial for saving CPU.Split a stereo signal into two mono channels. Useful when you want to process individual channels separately. Mixdown a stereo signal to mono.Reduces the stereo signal width (i.e. L/R channel differences) by an adjustable amount.
If one channel is the perfectly phase-reversed (inverted, negated) version of the other channel, setting Width to zero will result in no sound output. Converts pitch CV signal to linear frequency.Converts linear frequency to pitch CV signal.Turn incoming MIDI data into corresponding CV signals: Gate, pitch and velocity.]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/convert.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/CONVERT.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AU]]></title><description><![CDATA[A container module for FX type Audio Unit plugins. You may map up to 16 AU parameters to Drambo knobs. Open AU editor, press MAP and nudge params or tap on the first parameter under the MAP button to see a list of available params.A container module for FX type Audio Unit plugins. You may map up to 16 AU parameters to Drambo knobs. Open AU editor, press MAP and nudge params or tap on the first parameter under the MAP button to see a list of available params.A container module for MIDI type Audio Unit plugins. You may map up to 16 AU parameters to Drambo knobs. Open AU editor, press MAP and nudge params or tap on the first parameter under]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/au.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/AU.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[AMP]]></title><description><![CDATA[A DC-coupled signal amplifier and attenuator.Available Gain range is between "silence" and +12dB. Gain can be modulated and a VU style bar shows the module's output level including any DC offset, if present.A signal scaler that can boost or attenuate a signal.Range is the preamp gain, it can also be a negative number like -0.34.An amplifier controlled by a classic Attack/Decay envelope.An amplifier controlled by a classic
Attack/Decay/Sustain/Release envelope.An amplifier controlled by a classic Attack/Decay envelope where each parameter can be modulated.Provides stereo panning. ]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/amp.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/AMP.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Modules]]></title><description><![CDATA[
<a data-href="AMP" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/amp.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AMP</a>
<br><a data-href="AU" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/au.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">AU</a>
<br><a data-href="CONVERT" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/convert.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CONVERT</a>
<br><a data-href="CV" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/cv.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CV</a>
<br><a data-href="ENV" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/env.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">ENV</a>
<br><a data-href="FILTER" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/filter.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">FILTER</a>
<br><a data-href="FX" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/fx.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">FX</a>
<br><a data-href="LFO" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/lfo.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">LFO</a>
<br><a data-href="MATH" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/math.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">MATH</a>
<br><a data-href="MIDI" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/midi.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">MIDI</a>
<br><a data-href="MIXER" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/mixer.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">MIXER</a>
<br><a data-href="OSC" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/osc.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">OSC</a>
<br><a data-href="RACK" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/rack.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">RACK</a>
<br><a data-href="SAMPLER" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/sampler.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">SAMPLER</a>
<br><a data-href="SEQ" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/seq.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">SEQ</a>
<br><a data-href="SHAPER" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/shaper.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">SHAPER</a>
<br><a data-href="UI" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/ui.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">UI</a>
<br><a data-href="UTILS" href="00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/utils.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">UTILS</a>
]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/modules/modules.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Modules/Modules.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Songs]]></title><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/songs/songs.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Songs/Songs.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:38:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tags]]></title><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/tags/tags.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Tags/Tags.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Patches]]></title><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/patches/patches.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Patches/Patches.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:33:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Templates]]></title><description><![CDATA[%% Landmark %&lt;% tp.file.cursor(1) %&gt;%]]></description><link>00-drambo-cookbook/drambo-notes/templates/templates.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00-Drambo Cookbook/Drambo Notes/Templates/Templates.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 05:33:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>